Finding aid for the American Composers Forum Los Angeles Chapter records, 2000-2005 LSC.1974
UCLA Library Special Collections
American Composers Forum Los Angeles Chapter records
1906-2007
2000-2005
UCLA Library Special Collections
LSC.1974
13.7 Linear Feet (21 document boxes and 4 record cartons)
The American Composers Forum is a national organization that provides opportunities for composers to create and engage their communities in artistic creation and performance. The organization supports composers at all stages in their careers through grants, commissions, performance programs, and educational workshops. The Forum also works to foster an appreciation for new music while developing the next generation of composers, musicians, and communities. Included in the collection are administrative documents covering Heidi Lesemann's tenure with ACF-LA, as well as distribution materials and e-mail correspondence between members regarding various outreach projects and music events in the Los Angeles area. Furthermore, a series dedicated to Leonard Stein—musicologist and former director of the Arnold Schoenberg Institute at the University of Southern California— provides a wealth of research materials on pioneering contemporary music composers Arnold Schoenberg and Pierre Boulez.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
CONTAINS DIGITAL MATERIALS: This collection contains processed digital materials. All requests to access digital materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
Provenance/Source of Acquisition
The collection was donated in 2011 by Heidi Lesemann, director of the Los Angeles chapter of the American Composers Forum from 2000 to 2005.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 9970418173606533
Biography/History
In 1973, a group of graduate students in composition at the University of Minnesota created the Minnesota Composers Forum using a $400 grant from the University's Student Club Activities Fund. In 1996, the organization changed its name to the American Composers Forum, and eventually established local chapters in New York City, Boston, Philadelphia, Washington D.C., Atlanta, Chicago, San Francisco, and Los Angeles. Through granting, commissioning, and performance programs, the over 2,000 member national Forum provides composers at all stages of their careers with valuable resources for professional and artistic development. By linking non-profit arts organizations with composers and performers, the Forum fosters a demand for new music, enriches communities, and helps develop the next generation of composers, musicians, and music patrons.
The Los Angeles chapter was created by Heidi Lesemann—an experienced worker in various non-profit arts organizations—who served as director from 2000 to 2005, with composer Karl Montevirgen as assistant director. Their tenure with the ACF resulted in a wealth of outreach and education programs including the Subito professional advancement grant program for composers, as well as educational residencies at various K-12 schools. Furthermore, they established a strong community of composers, performers and educators in the Los Angeles area through the Composers Salons workshop series and the New Music LA annotated calendar of new music events in Southern California. While the chapter initially received financial support from organizations such as the California Arts Council and the National Endowment for the Arts, these funds grew increasingly difficult to come by in later years, and the chapter now functions primarily on a volunteer-based level through online message boards and e-mail listservs.
Scope and Content
Collection primarily consists of promotional materials, administrative documents, financial reports, membership files, program reports, and correspondence created during Heidi Lesemann's tenure with the American Composers Forum Los Angeles chapter, 2000 to 2005. There are materials related to the Los Angeles chapter's formation, annual budget reports, planning for the chapter website, and membership e-mail lists. Of particular research interest are the New Music LA calendars—a comprehensive bi-monthly calendar of music events in the Southern California area, featuring a guest editorial focusing on issues of local concern. Also included in the collection are personal composer applications for outreach initiatives such as the Composers Suitcase educational residency and the Subito grant program, with proposed projects and sample curriculum.
Organization and Arrangement
Arranged in four series:
1. Organization and Outreach, 2000-2005
2. Events, 2000-2005
3. Administrative, 1999-2007
4. Leonard Stein papers, 1906-1988
All series are arranged alphabetically.
Related Material
The following sources provide additional information on the classical and "New Music" scenes in Los Angeles:
Leonard Stein Papers, 1930-2004 (PASC-M 270) at UCLA Library Special Collections
Lawrence Morton papers, 1908-1987 (1522) at UCLA Library Special Collections
Monday Evening Concerts of Los Angeles Programs, 1971- (1160) at UCLA Library Special Collections
Ojai Music Festival Records, 1940- (PASC-M 277) at UCLA Library Special Collections
Betty Freeman papers, 1965-2008 (MSS 227) at UCSD Library Special Collections
Leonard Stein papers, 1942-1983 (MSS 219) at UCSD Library Special Collections
Peter Yates papers, 1927-1976 (MSS 0014) at UCSD Library Special Collections
- Series 1: Outreach & Education, 2000-2005
  Scope and Content
  Series comprises mixed materials related to the various outreach and education projects directed by Heidi Lesemann and ACF-LA from 2000 to 2005. There is a sizable amount of personal applications for the Composer's Suitcase—an educational program in which composers donated music curriculum, instruments, and resource materials for elementary school teachers—as well as Subito—a grant program for California-based composers and musicians. The lesson plans, sample curricula, and musical activities contained within the Composer's Suitcase files are particularly useful music education tools, while the Subito grant applications contain compositions and press kits from aspiring composers and musicians.
  - Buckley School: Call for Composers, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Buckley School: Contracts: Huang, Joan, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Buckley School: Contracts: Lockwood, Stephen, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Classical Music Consumer Segmentation Study, 2002 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
    Includes 1 DVD.
    Special equipment or further processing may be required for viewing. To access digital materials you must notify the reference desk in advance of your visit.
  - Commissioning Possibilities, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Community Partners: Contracts, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Composer's Commissioning Program (CCP): Call for Composers, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Composer's Datebook: Proposal, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Composer's Suitcase: California Arts Council (CAC): Contract, 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Composer's Suitcase: California Arts Council (CAC): Contract, 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Composer's Suitcase: California Arts Council (CAC): Final Evaluation, 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Composer's Suitcase: California Arts Council (CAC): Final Evaluation, 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Composer's Suitcase: California Arts Council (CAC): Project Presentation, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Composer's Suitcase: California Arts Council (CAC): Proposal (1 of 2), 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Composer's Suitcase: California Arts Council (CAC): Proposal (2 of 2), 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Composer's Suitcase: California Arts Council (CAC): Proposal (1 of 2), 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Composer's Suitcase: California Arts Council (CAC): Proposal (2 of 2), 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Composer's Suitcase: California Arts Council (CAC): Proposal, 2003-2004 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Composer's Suitcase: Call for Composers, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Composer's Suitcase: Composer Selection: Photographs, 2001 June (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Composer's Suitcase: Composer Feedback, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Composer's Suitcase: Composer Interviews, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Composer's Suitcase: Composers: Albert, Adrienne, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Composer's Suitcase: Composers: Fernandez, Robert, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Composer's Suitcase: Composers: George, Ron, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Composer's Suitcase: Composers: George, Ron: Photographs, 2002 April (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Composer's Suitcase: Composers: Kelly, Thomas, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Composer's Suitcase: Composers: Kelly, Thomas: Photographs, 2000s (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Composer's Suitcase: Composers: Knoles, Amy, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Composer's Suitcase: Composers: Kouneva, Penka, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Composer's Suitcase: Composers: Kouneva, Penka: Photographs, 2002 April (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Composer's Suitcase: Composers: Lechusza, Alan, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Composer's Suitcase: Composers: Lechusza, Ala: Photographs, 2003 January (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Composer's Suitcase: Composers: Madsen, Pamela, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Composer's Suitcase: Composers: McAuley, Jim, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Composer's Suitcase: Composers: Morito, Yumika, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Composer's Suitcase: Composers: Morito, Yukima: Photographs, 2003 May (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Composer's Suitcase: Composers: Osuna, Tommy, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Composer's Suitcase: Composers: Pourafar, Pirayeh, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Composer's Suitcase: Composers: Pourafar, Pirayeh and husband: Photographs, 2003 May (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Composer's Suitcase: Composers: Renteria, Andres, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Composer's Suitcase: Composers: Ron, Yuval, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Composer's Suitcase: Composers: Suter, Anthony, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Composer's Suitcase: Lesson Plans, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Composer's Suitcase: Newspaper Clippings, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Composer's Suitcase: Orientation and Evaluation: Photographs, 2001-2002 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Composer's Suitcase: Photographs, 2003 June (Box 22, Folder 9)
    1 Kodak picture CD.
  - Composer's Suitcase: Press Conference Materials, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Composer's Suitcase: Press Conference Photographs, 2001 September (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Composer's Suitcase: Teachers: Orientation Materials, 2001-2003 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Composer's Suitcase: Teachers: Receipts, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Composer's Suitcase: Teachers: Reid, Nancy, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Composition Competitions, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Distribution Materials, 2003 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Faith Partners: Call for Composers and Venues, 2001-2002 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Faith Partners: Distribution Materials, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Faith Partners: Proposal, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - National: Sample Forms, undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - New Band Horizons: Proposal, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Poseidon School: Applications, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Poseidon School: Contracts: Beasley, Fletcher, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Poseidon School: Contracts: McAuley, Jim, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Poseidon School: Contracts: Fernandez, Robert, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Poseidon School: Contracts: George, Ron, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Poseidon School: Lesson Plans, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Poseiden School: Photographs, 2002 June (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Poseidon School: Proposal, 2001-2003 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Press Kit, undated (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Subito: Administrative, 2003-2007 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Subito: Announcement, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Subito: Application Forms, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Subito: Composers: Amigo, Cristian, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Subito: Composers: Argilla, Steven, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Subito: Composers: Auralia Composers Collective, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Subito: Composers: Aushalomov, David, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Subito: Composers: Au Yong, Byron, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Subito: Composers: Azzam, Nabil, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Subito: Composers: Bailey, Stephanie, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Subito: Composers: Beck, Jeremy, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Subito: Composers: Belling, Cary, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Subito: Composers: Benoit, David, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Subito: Composers: Bernard, Cindy, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Subito: Composers: Bernard, Cindy, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Subito: Composers: Bialosky, Marshall, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Subito: Composers: Brown, Oscar, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Subito: Composers: Burns, Benedict, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Subito: Composers: Butler, Steve, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Subito: Composers: Carney, James, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Subito: Composers: Cohn, Stephen, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Subito: Composers: Cox, Robin, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Subito: Composers: Cox, Robin, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Subito: Composers: Cox, Robin, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Subito: Composers: Durkin, Andrew, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Subito: Composers: Durkin, Andrew, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Subito: Composers: EarJam, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Subito: Composers: Eisenstadt, Harris, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Subito: Composers: Frank, Lawrence, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Subito: Composers: Garretson, Weba, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Subito: Composers: Garretson, Weba, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Subito: Composers: George, Ron, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Subito: Composers: Gerberg, Miriam, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Subito: Composers: Grasse, Jonathan, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Subito: Composers: Greco, Christopher, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Subito: Composers: Hart, Karen, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Subito: Composers: Heasley, Tom, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Subito: Composers: Herring-Colon, Jose, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Subito: Composers: Hurley, Susan, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Subito: Composers: Ingala Jr., Rocco, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Subito: Composers: Jarvinen, Arthur, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Subito: Composers: Karush, Larry, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Subito: Composers: Kendrick, Eva, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Subito: Composers: Kinney, Andrew, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Subito: Composers: Kouneva, Penka, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Subito: Composers: Kraft, William, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Subito: Composers: Krausas, Veronika, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Subito: Composers: Lacques, Paul, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Subito: Composers: LaBelle, Brandon, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Subito: Composers: Leader, Brian, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Subito: Composers: Leavitt, William, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Subito: Composers: Los Angeles Flute Quartet, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Subito: Composers: Ludwin, Norman, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Subito: Composers: Madsen, Pamela, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Subito: Composers: Naidoo, Shaun, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Subito: Composers: Newmark, Mary-Lou, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Subito: Composers: New Town Pasadena Foundation, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Subito: Composers: Pompey, Tim, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Subito: Composers: Price, Deon, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Subito: Composers: Price, Deon, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Subito: Composers: Price, Deon, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Subito: Composers: Ron, Yuval, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Subito: Composers: Roper, William, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Subito: Composers: Rothbaum, David, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Subito: Composers: Rothmann, Daniel, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Subito: Composers: Roze, Christopher, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Subito: Composers: Rudolph, Adam, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Subito: Composers: Rudolph, Adam, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Subito: Composers: Roustom, Kareem, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Subito: Composers: Schrader, Barry, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Subito: Composers: Sekiya, Naomi, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Subito: Composers: Shapiro, Alex, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Subito: Composers: Sherr, David, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Subito: Composers: Steinmetz, John, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Subito: Composers: Steinmetz, John, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Subito: Composers: Trayle, Mark, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Subito: Composers: Troy, T.J., 2001 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Subito: Composers: Wadle, Douglas C., 2003 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Subito: Composers: Walker, Daniel, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Subito: Composers: Wolfgang, Gernot, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Subito: Composers: Yamami, Bryan, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Subito: Composers: Zvonar, Richard, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Subito: Review Panel, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Subito: Testimonials, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Series 2: Events, 2000-2005
  Series comprises distribution materials and printed email correspondence related to various concerts, festivals, and workshops directed or attended by members of ACF-LA. Of particular significance to the researcher are the New Music LA brochures—comprehensive, annotated calendars of new music events in the Southern California area from 2000 to 2004, initiated by Heidi Lesemann and edited by the late Los Angeles-based music critic Alan Rich.
  - California Arts Council Talk: Photographs, 2000s (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Composer to Composer: Salonen: Photographs, 2002 May (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Composers Salon: Photographs, 2002 June (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Composers Salon: Preston, Don: Photographs, 2000s (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Concerts: The Getty Composium: Proposal, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Concerts: Knitting Factory: Proposal, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Concerts: Salon #2, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Concerts: Special Salon, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Conferences: American Composers Forum: Photos, 2001 July (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Conferences: California Arts Council, Arts in Education: Evaluation, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Conferences: California Arts Council, Arts in Education: Program, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Conferences: California Arts Council, Arts in Education: Resources, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Conferences: International Association for Jazz Education (IAJE), 2002 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Conferences: IAJE: Photographs, 2002 Jaunary 8 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    Also includes "Meeting and Awards" photographs dated February 2002.
  - Conferences: Model Arts Program (MAP), 2002 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Conferences: WestEd: Planning, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Conferences: WestEd: Program, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Conferences: WestEd: Project Descriptions, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Conferences: WestEd: Resources, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Continental Harmony: Distribution Materials, 2000-2005 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Enclosure 3: Harry Partch Archive, by Philip Blackburn, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Festivals: American Composers: Program, 2003 (Box 22, Folder 20)
    Includes 1 CD.
  - Festivals: Electric Orange Festival, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Festivals: International Women's Day, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Festivals: Ojai Music Festival, 1974-1978 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Festivals: Ojai: Distribution Materials, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Festivals: Ojai: Distribution Materials, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Festivals: Ojai: Photo Collage, 2002 June (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Festivals: Ojai: Planning, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Festivals: Ojai: Programs, 1954-1964 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Festivals: Ojai: Programs, 1965-1969 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Festivals: Ojai: Programs, 1971-1976 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Festivals: Ojai: Programs, 1977-1983 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Festivals: Ojai: Programs, 1984-1989 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Festivals: Ojai: Programs, 1991-1994 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Festivals: Sonic Circuits: Innova Recordings, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Festivals: Sonic Circuits: Planning, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Festivals: Sonic Circuits: VIII, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Festivals: Sonic Circuits: IX, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Grammy Fest: Proposal, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Making Music: O., [David]: Photographs, 2003 April (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Music Room: Photographs, 2003 March 9 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Music Room with Pierre Boulez: Invitation, 2003 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - New Music LA: Brochures, 2002-2003 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - New Music LA: Calendars, 2000 September-October (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - New Music LA: Calendars, 2000 May-June (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - New Music LA: Calendars, 2000 November-December (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - New Music LA: Calendars, 2001 January-February (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - New Music LA: Calendars, 2001 March-April (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - New Music LA: Calendars, 2001 May-June (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - New Music LA: Calendars, 2001 September-October (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - New Music LA: Calendars, 2001 November-December (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - New Music LA: Calendars, 2002 January-February (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - New Music LA: Calendars, 2002 March-April (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - New Music LA: Calendars, 2002 May-August (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - New Music LA: Calendars, 2002 September-October (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - New Music LA: Calendars, 2002 November-December (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - New Music LA: Calendars, 2003 January-February (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - New Music LA: Calendars, 2003 March-April (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - New Music LA: Calendars, 2003 May-August (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - New Music LA: Calendars, 2003 September-October (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - New Music LA: Calendars, 2003 November-December (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - New Music LA: Calendars, 2004 January-February (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - New Music LA: Calendars, 2004 March-April (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - New Music LA: Planning, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - New Music LA: Proposal, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - New Music LA: Reviews, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Pierre Boulez Award: Photographs, 2003 May (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Poseidon School Graduation: Photographs, 2002 June (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Workshops: American Music Center (AMC): Distribution Materials, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Workshops: American Music Center (AMC): Synergy, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Workshops: American Music Center (AMC): USC Series, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Workshops: Aurelia, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Workshops: CalState Los Angeles, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Workshops: Public Relations, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Workshops: Public Relations: Photographs, 2002 May (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Workshops: Tekworx, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 17)
- Series 3: Administrative, 1999-2007
  Series comprises administrative records from both the Los Angeles chapter of the ACF and the national body, spanning the years 1999 to 2007. Monthly reports, chapter sponsors, and meeting minutes from both the Los Angeles chapter and the national organization are contained within the series. Of particular significance to the researcher are the membership files, which contain composer biographies, audio recordings, and e-mail address lists.
  SERIES CONTAINS DIGITAL MATERIALS: Special equipment or further processing may be required for viewing. To access digital materials you must notify the reference desk in advance of your visit.
  - Advisory Board: Meetings: Miscellaneous, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Board of Directors: Handbook: Board and Staff Contact Info, 2003-2004 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Board of Directors: Handbook: Fundraising, 2000-2004 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Board of Directors: Handbook: Legal Documents, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Board of Directors: Handbook: Operational Plan, 2005 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Board of Directors: Handbook: Organization, 1999-2003 (Box 11, Folder 1)